http://www.era404.com/legal/privacy/

Contact Us
NavigationAboutOur MissionOur NetworkOur ProcessExecutive TeamClients / PartnersAwards / RecognitionTestimonialsCreative ReelPortfolioPrint DesignIdentity DesignDigital MediaStrategyMotion GraphicsEnvironmentalMediaPress ReleasesNews ArticlesInfo ResourcesNewsletterContact Us
To Top
Privacy Policy
This privacy statement explains our methods of data gathering, the use of that data and how we protect data that we collect about you.
Recording of IP addresses and statistical monitoring
Internet Protocol (IP) addresses are used to connect your computer to the Internet, and are recorded by every site on the Internet. ERA404 uses web statistics software to gather and analyze anonymous activity information for statistical purposes and for administration of our web site and servers. The general information we collect is used to improve the content of our web pages and your navigation through our site. This software does not collect any personal information, and we do not record or store individual visitor profiles.
Cookies
Cookies are alphanumeric identifiers that are transferred to hard drives through web browsers to enable recognition of individual visitors. Cookies are not used on the ERA404 web site.
Registration and Order Forms
Visitors need not register to visit our home page and access information about the company. Some specific pages may require registration and the provision of personal contact data (such as name and email address). User-specific data volunteered by you when requesting trials, samples and product demonstrations is used to check your eligibility for a trial or to receive a sample and/or to bill you for products and services. The data is archived for marketing and sales internal use only and is not shared with other organizations unless you give your consent.
Financial Information
Our web site is not protected by the industry-standard Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) software, so we only accept financial information (such as credit card numbers) via fax or email directly from the authorized card holder. This data is not shared with other organizations, except when transmitting the credit card number to the appropriate credit card company during order processing. The data is archived electronically and in paper format, for internal accounting use only.
Opt-Out Consent
In accordance with the requirements of the Data Protection Act 1998, we provide the opportunity for you to opt out of certain types of usage of your personal data when supplied to us via registration and order forms. Should you wish your personal data to be removed from our records or updated at a later date, you can request this by emailing us with our contact form.
Use of Data
Any data gathered through the ERA404 web site is usually used for internal purposes only. This data is not usually shared with other organizations, unless this is necessary for the formation and/or completion of a contract. In the unlikely event that ERA404 or substantially all of its assets are acquired by a third party, customer data will of course be one of the transferred assets.
Data Quality and Access
ERA404 takes reasonable steps to ensure that the data we maintain are accurate, complete and timely for the purposes for which they are used. We also take reasonable precautions to protect it from loss, misuse or alteration.
Your Consent to this Policy
By using our web site, you consent to the collection and use of your data by ERA404 as specified above. Your visit and any dispute over privacy is subject to this Policy and our disclaimer. Should we decide to change our privacy policy we will post all changes on this page so that you are always kept aware of how we use any data you provide to us.
Legal Information
Copyright
Terms of Use
Privacy Policy
Recent Media
Herb Ritts at Home
Press:
April 12th, 2020
Streamlining Internal Workflows
News:
April 03rd, 2019
Stafflist Demo
Info:
February 18th, 2019
Designing Data
News:
November 16th, 2018
Mobile App Design & Development
News:
April 04th, 2018
ERA404 to Sunset PANTONE Moods
Press:
March 16th, 2018
How BULC CLUB Works
Press:
August 08th, 2017
FileChecker WordPress Plugin
News:
© Copyright 2020  ·  era404 Creative Group, Inc  ·  Terms of Use  ·  Privacy Policy
